Finding Aid for Vice President and Chief Financial Officer (University of Michigan) Records, 1909-2006
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Assistant to the Vice President and Chief Financial Officer
  - Topical Files, 1940-1988
    - 1940-1988
      - Capital Program Review, Staff Meeting, 1964 (Box 78)
      - Central Campus Block Study, 1959 (Box 78)
      - Central Campus Building Site Inventory, 1975 (Box 78)
      - Central Campus Plan Study, Regents' Communication, July 1963 (Box 78)
      - Child Care Center, 1969-1971 (Box 78)
      - Child Care Services Task Force, 1980-1981 (Box 79)
      - Construction Management, 1974-1977 (Box 79)
      - Corporate Responsibility, 1970-1977 (Box 79)
      - Endowed Chairs and Named Chairs, 1977-1983 (Box 79)
      - Exterior Elements Design Review Committee, 1968 (Box 79)
      - Fresh Air Camp, 1967-1988 (Box 79)
      - Fuller Road Recreational Facilities, 1966-1980 (Box 79)
      - Fuller Road Study, 1960-1980; 3 folders (Box 79)
      - Hill Auditorium, History of, 1977 (Box 79)
      - Historic Preservation, 1972-1984 (Box 79)
      - Historic Preservation-Central Campus Historic District, 1976-1979; 2 folders (Box 79)
      - Housing Division, Staff Review and Charge, 1981 (Box 79)
      - Informational Center on the Diagonal, 1964-1968 (Box 79)
      - 1958-1984, 10 folders (Box 79)
      - Land Maps, 1940-1967 (Box 79)
      - Landscape Review, 1965-1968 (Box 80)
      - Low Income Housing Property Sale, Green Road and Baxter, 1967-1968 (Box 80)
      - Michigan Environmental Assessment, 1976 (Box 80)
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 80)
      - Non-recurring Fund Allocation, 1981 (Box 80)
      - North Campus
        - Commercial Center, 1965-1973; 1983 (Box 80)
        - Development, General, 1957-1984; 2 folders (Box 80)
        - Fraternity Area, 1956-1969; 4 folders (Box 80)
        - Land Dispositions, 1952-1976 (Box 80)
        - Plan Study, 1959-1960; 1978; 1983 (Box 80)
        - Religious Center, 1956-1971 (Box 80)
        - Roads and Utilities, 1956-1965 (Box 80)
      - North Campus Task Force (to review the impact of the Engineering College's move to North Campus), 1981-1983 (Box 80)
      - Northwood Community Center, 1967-1973 (Box 80)
      - Plant Extension Committee
        - 1970-1981, 15 folders (Box 80)
      - Plant Operations Review Committee-Background Materials, 1981 (Box 81)
      - Plant Operations Review Committee-Minutes, 1981-1982; 3 folders (Box 81)
      - Police and Security Study, 1973-1974 (Box 81)
      - Population and Traffic Studies, 1960-1965 (Box 81)
      - President's House, 1980 (Box 81)
      - Property Acquisition, Summary Lists, 1966-1978; 1984 (Box 81)
      - Public Housing Eligibility Study, 1968-1971 (Box 81)
      - Regental Construction Policies, 1975 (Box 81)
      - Regents' Retreat, June 1971 (Box 81)
      - Retirement Housing, 1976-1980 (Box 81)
      - SACUA (Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs)
        - Faculty Center Committee, 1960-1968 (Box 81)
        - Senate Assembly Advisory Committee on Financial Affairs, 1981-1986; 5 folders (Box 81)
        - Senate Assembly Advisory Committee on Financial Affairs, 1971-1981; 15 folders (Box 82)
          - South African Investment Advisory Committee, 1979 (Box 82)
        - Senate Assembly Committee on Campus Planning and Development, 1967-1970; 9 folders (Box 82)
        - Senate Assembly Committee on Campus Planning and Development, 1955-1966; 8 folders (Box 83)
      - Search Committees
        - Associate Director for Affirmative Action, 1987-1988 (Box 76)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1 2018 ]
        - Director of Business Operations, 1988 (Box 76)
        - General Counsel, 1986-1987 (Box 76)
      - Student Vehicle Regulations, 1959-1968; 3 folders (Box 83)
      - Television Facilities, 1960-1974; 3 folders (Box 83)
      - University-City Council Annual Dinner Meeting with Regents, 1967-1968; 2 folders (Box 83)
      - University-City Council Quarterly Conference Dinner Meetings, 1966-1969; 3 folders (Box 83)
      - University-City Relations
        - City-University Coordinating Committee, 1963-1966; 1979-1986; 4 folders (Box 83)
        - General, 1968-1978; 3 folders (Box 83)
        - General, 1952-1967; 9 folders (Box 84)
        - Joint Committee on Student Driving Regulations, 1968-1969 (Box 84)
        - Police and Fire Protection Services, 1971-1975 (Box 84)
      - University Council, 1970-1971; 1984-1985 (Box 84)
      - University Housing
        - Additional Student Housing, 1976-1977; 2 folders (Box 84)
        - General, 1955-1982; 2 folders (Box 84)
        - Historical and Building Data, 1964-1982; 4 folders (Box 84)
        - Housing Policy (including U of M employees), 1964-1970 (Box 84)
        - Housing Study, 1965-1967 (Box 84)
        - Student Housing
          - Alpha Epsilon Pi Fraternity, 1970 (Box 84)
          - Housing Space Issue, 1975-1976; 2 folders (Box 84)
          - Sigma Alpha Mu, 1970 (Box 84)
          - Sigma Chi and Alpha Delta Phi Fraternities, 1964-1965 (Box 84)
          - State and Hill Street Fraternities, 1963-1981 (Box 84)
      - University-Industry Task Force, 1980-1984 (Box 84)
      - University Lands Committee, 1972-1983; 2 folders (Box 84)
- Associate Vice President for Finance
  - Topical Files, 1996-2006
    The files of the Associate Vice President for Finance Topical Files (15 linear feet) date from Timothy Slottow's term in that position, 1998-2003. As with the earlier accession of files from the Assistant to the Vice President and Chief Executive Officer in 1996, these files augment the main topical files received in previous accessions, but also include documentation unique to the assistant position. One particularly interesting set of files relate to the university's investments in Information Technology in the late 1990s and early 2000s.
    - 1996-2006, 1998-2003
      - ABC Activity Analysis / Activity Based, 2003
        - General (Box 144)
        - Grant Thornton LLP (Box 144)
        - Non PO Voucher Process (Box 144)
        - Property Leasing Process (Box 144)
      - A-133, 2000-2002; 2 folders (Box 144)
      - Academic Affairs -- Admissions Collegent, 2002-2004 (Box 144)
      - Accenture, 2002-2003 (Box 144)
      - Acts, 2002 (Box 144)
        (USA Patriot and Sarbonas-Oxley)
      - Acumen Contract, 1999-2001 (Box 144)
      - Adaytum Software, 2000-2001 (Box 144)
      - ADDAG (Administrative Data Delivery Advisory Group), 2001-2003 (Box 144)
      - Aerospace Engineering (Michigan Mars Rover Project),2001 (Box 144)
      - AFLAC, 2001 (Box 144)
      - Alumni Association, 2002-2004
        - General (Box 144)
        - Alumni Association Closing (Box 144)
        - MBNA (Box 144)
      - AAUP (American Association of University Professors), 2002 (Box 144)
      - Ann Arbor City of, 1996-2002
        - General (Box 144)
        - General Information (Box 144)
        - Public Schools (Box 144)
        - Things to Do (Box 144)
      - Ann Arbor City Relations, 2000-2002 (Box 144)
      - Ann Arbor Summer Festival, 2000-2002 (Box 144)
      - Announcements, 1999-2006 (Box 144)
      - Annual Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 144)
      - Annual Reports, Other Colleges and Universities, 2001 (Box 144)
      - Athletics, 2003 (Box 144)
      - Athletics, 2002
        - General (Box 144)
        - FY 03 Budgets (Box 144)
        - Contracts (Box 145)
        - Football Tickets Pricing (Box 145)
        - Recreational Sports Capital Plan (Box 145)
        - Intercollegiate Athletics Capital Plan (Box 145)
      - Audit, PricewaterhouseCoopers
        - FY, 2003
          - General (Box 145)
          - Engagement Letter (Box 145)
        - FY, 2002
          - Management Observations, 2 folders (Box 145)
          - General (Box 145)
          - Audit Committee Charters (Box 145)
          - Contracts (Box 145)
          - Engagement Letter (Box 145)
      - Audits, University
        - FY, 2003; 2 folders (Box 145)
        - FY -- Office, 2002; 2 folders (Box 145)
      - Banks, 1999-2002 (Box 146)
        - Bank Accounts (Box 146)
        - Banking Service Agreements (Box 146)
        - Bank One (Box 146)
        - Brokerage Accounts (Box 146)
        - Contracts (Box 146)
        - National City Bank (Box 146)
      - Benefits, 1998-2004
        - General (Box 146)
        - Life Insurance (Box 146)
        - Other Post Retirement Benefits (OPEB) (Box 146)
        - Pharmacy Carve Out (Box 146)
        - Plan Prescriptions (Box 146)
        - Prescription Drug Work Group Report (Box 146)
        - Prudential Insurance Company (Box 146)
        - Recharges (Box 146)
        - Reserves (Box 146)
        - Review (Box 146)
      - Biomedical Sciences Research Building (BSRB), 2002-2003
        - General (Box 146)
        - BSRB Reporting Requirements (Box 146)
      - Borrowing Policies and Procedures, UM, 2002 (Box 146)
      - Broadcast/Media, University, 2000-2004
        - Broadcast Assets Assessment Team, 2 folders (Box 146)
        - WUOM / WFUM, 2 folders (Box 146)
      - Budget FY, 2004
        - General (Box 147)
        - State Budget Request (Box 147)
      - Budget, 2002-2003
        - AVPF (Box 147)
        - AVPF Budget Meetings (Box 147)
        - General Fund (Box 147)
        - State Budget Report (Box 147)
        - Abruzzi, Phil (Box 147)
      - Budget FY General Fund, 2002 (Box 147)
      - Buildings, 2002-2003
        - Great Lakes (Box 147)
        - Herbert H. Dow and G. G. Brown Building (Box 147)
        - Hill Auditorium (Box 147)
        - Horace H. Rackham Educational Memorial Building (Box 147)
        - "L" shaped Building or Undergraduate Science Building (Box 147)
          (USB)
        - Perry Addition (Box 147)
        - Planada Apartments (Box 147)
      - Building Approval Process, 2002 (Box 147)
      - Business Continuity Plans, 2001-2003 (Box 147)
      - Business and Finance, 2002-2004
        - General (Box 147)
        - Training and Tracking Career Competency Team (Box 147)
      - Business School, 2000-2003
        - General (Box 147)
        - Dixon Doll (Box 147)
        - Hong Kong Operations (Box 147)
        - Wolverine Venture Fund, 2 folders (Box 147)
      - Camp Michigania, 1999-2002 (Box 147)
      - Campuses, University, 2000-2003
        - Dearborn (Box 147)
        - Dearborn Greenway Project (Box 147)
        - Flint, 2 folders (Box 147)
        - Flint / Dearborn UIP (Box 148)
        - Housing -- Economic Feasibility -- Flint (Box 148)
        - Policy Issues (Box 148)
        - Dearborn Fairlane Training and Development Center, 3 folders (Box 148)
        - Ford Training Development Center (Box 148)
      - Cash Forecast, 2001-2002; 2 folders (Box 148)
      - Cash Management, 1997-2001 (Box 148)
      - Cash Reconciliation, 1999 (Box 148)
      - Chronological File
        - 2003 (Box 148)
        - 2002 (Box 148)
      - Citibank, 1998 (Box 148)
      - CMS Energy Corporation, 2001 (Box 148)
      - Common Fund, 2001-2002
      - Construction, 2001-2002
        - General (Box 149)
        - Legal Costs (Box 149)
      - Deans, Directors, Department Heads (3D), 2001-2003 (Box 149)
      - Debt, University, 2000-2003
        - General (Box 149)
        - S&P and Moody's re: Bond Issues (Box 149)
        - Bonds, May 2002 (Box 149)
        - Box 149 Bonds Due Dilligence, May 2002 (Box 149)
        - Bond Purchase Agreement, May 13, 2003 (Box 149)
        - Bond and Tax Arbitrage (Box 149)
        - College of Engineering (Box 149)
        - Dearborn Debt Analysis (Box 149)
        - Debt Policy (Box 149)
        - Hospital Revenue (Box 149)
        - Investment of Borrowed Funds (Box 149)
        - Liquidation (Box 149)
        - Medical Service Plan Revenue (Box 149)
        - Rating / Ratios (Box 149)
        - Refinancing of Commercial Paper -- General Revenue (Box 149)
        - SEC Annual Filings (Box 149)
        - State Building Authority Projects (Box 149)
        - Trustee Letters (Box 149)
        - UM Official Statement, May 2002 (Box 149)
      - Delegation of Authority
        - 2003 (Box 149)
        - 2002 (Box 149)
      - Department of Health and Human Services (DHHS), 1999-2004
        - General, 2 folders (Box 150)
        - Subpoena (Box 150)
      - Dentistry, School of, 2002 (Box 150)
      - Development Office, 1999-2004
        - General (Box 150)
        - Gifts of Buildings (Box 150)
        - Evaluation of Planned Giving Program (Box 150)
        - Naming Building Guidelines (Box 150)
        - Campaign Funding (Box 150)
        - Helmut Stern (Box 150)
        - Palmer House (Box 150)
      - Divestments, 2002-2003
        - Israel (Box 150)
        - Tobacco (Box 150)
      - Division of Student Affairs (DSA), 1999 (Box 150)
      - Economic Impacts, 1999-2001
        - Economic Impact on Budget (Box 150)
        - Economic Impact of, 9/11 (Box 150)
      - Emergency Disaster Plans, 2001-2003 (Box 150)
        (see also Business Continuity Plans file)
      - Endowments, University, 1998-2004
        - General (Box 150)
        - Distribution Policy (Box 150)
        - Endowment Policy (Box 150)
        - Market Valuation (Box 150)
      - Engineering, College of, 2002
        - General (Box 150)
        - Yellow Submarine (Box 150)
      - Enrollment Reports, 2002 (Box 150)
      - Environmental Impairment Liability, 2001-2003
        - General (Box 150)
        - Environmental Liability Account (ELA) (Box 150)
      - Escheats, 2001 (Box 150)
      - Facilities and Operations, 2000-2004
        - General (Box 150)
        - DPS Investigations (Box 150)
        - DTE Energy Complaint (Box 150)
        - Lab Renovations Process (Box 150)
        - Parking Services (Box 151)
        - Plant (Box 151)
        - Plant Extension (Box 151)
        - Transportation Services (Box 151)
        - Use and Finance Statements (Box 151)
      - Financial Reports, 2002-2004; 3 folders (Box 151)
      - General Counsel, 2001-2003
        - General (Box 151)
        - University Club (Box 151)
        - Hill Auditorium (Box 151)
        - Consultants / Independent Contractors (Box 151)
        - Contracts (Box 151)
      - Gifts, 2001-2003
        - 2003 (Box 151)
        - 2002 (Box 151)
        - Charitable Remainder (Box 151)
        - Deferred (Box 151)
        - Lincoln Knorr Trust (Box 151)
        - Merrill Lynch Letters (Box 151)
        - Roger McCarthy (Box 151)
      - Global Challenge, 2001 (Box 151)
      - Government Accounting Standards Board (GASB), 1995-2002
        - General (Box 151)
        - Scholarship Discounts (Box 151)
      - Health Insurance Portability and Accountability(HIPPA), 2001-2003 (Box 151)
      - Health Services Research Initiative (HSRI), 2001-2002 (Box 151)
      - Higher Education Survey, 2002 (Box 151)
      - Hospital and Health Systems, UM, 1999-2004
        - General (Box 151)
        - Academic Medical Centers (Box 151)
        - Accounts Receivable (Box 151)
        - Cardiovascular Center (CVC) and Parking (Box 152)
        - Capital Plan (Box 152)
        - Debt Capacity (Box 152)
        - Clinical Information Systems (CIS)
          - 2003 (Box 152)
          - 2002, 2 folders (Box 152)
        - Crosswalk and Utilities (Box 152)
        - East Ann Arbor Surgical Center (Box 152)
        - Financial Statements YE, 6/30/2002 (Box 152)
        - Hospital and Professional Liability Actuarial Analysis (Box 152)
        - Hospital Refinancing (Box 152)
        - Med Inn Building (Box 152)
        - Project Gemini (Box 152)
        - Strategic Plan (Box 152)
        - VA Space (Box 152)
      - Hospital Supply Management, 1999-2002 (Box 152)
      - Housing, 2001-2004
        - General (Box 152)
        - University (Box 152)
        - Nu Sigma Nu (Box 152)
        - Residence Halls -- Feasibility (Box 152)
        - Residential Life Initiatives (Box 152)
        - Capital Plan, 2 folders (Box 153)
      - Human Resources and Affirmative Action (HRAA), 1998-2005
        - General, 3 folders (Box 153)
        - Funding Pill Splitting and Levy Write-offs (Box 153)
        - Classification System Project, 2 folders (Box 153)
        - Development (Box 153)
        - Diversity (Box 153)
        - Employment and Executive Services (Box 153)
        - Effort Reporting (Box 153)
        - Executive Summary (Box 153)
        - Human Resource Pilot (Box 153)
        - LEO Contract (Box 153)
        - Strike Plan (Box 153)
        - Unit Assessment (Box 153)
        - Open and Wanted (Box 153)
        - Unfiled (Box 153)
      - Human Resources / Payroll Service Center, 2001-2002 (Box 153)
      - Human Resources / Metrics Project "Corporate Leadership Council,", 2002-2004
        - General (Box 153)
        - Contract (Box 153)
      - Indirect Cost Reimbursement Recovery (ICR)
        - 2003 (Box 154)
        - Historical (Box 154)
        - Recharge Rate (Box 154)
        - 2002, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Internal Controls, 2004
        - Internal Bank (Box 154)
      - Internal Revenue Service, 2001 (Box 154)
      - Institute for Social Research (ISR), 1999 (Box 154)
      - Investment Rating Agencies, 2002-2004
        - General (Box 154)
        - Moody's, 2 folders (Box 154)
        - Press Releases (Box 154)
        - Standard and Poors, 2 folders (Box 154)
      - Investment Office, 2001-2004
        - General (Box 154)
        - Cayman (Box 154)
        - Investments (Box 154)
        - Securities Lending Review (Box 154)
        - Securities (Box 154)
      - IT Communications, 1998-2005
        - General (Box 154)
        - Capital Plan (Box 154)
        - Data Systems Center (Box 155)
        - IT Communications Advisory Group (Box 155)
        - IT Communications Consulting, 2 folders (Box 155)
        - IT Diagnostic Report (Box 155)
        - IT Strategic Alliance (Box 155)
        - MiLR Regional Fiber-Optic Network Project (Box 155)
      - Ivory Book, 1999-2001 (Box 155)
      - Law School, 2002-2003
        - General (Box 155)
        - Addition Project (Box 155)
        - William W. Cook Trust (Box 155)
      - Laurentian, 2001-2002 (Box 155)
      - Legal, 2000-2002
        - Barris, Scott, Denn & Driker (Box 155)
        - TMP / Walbridge (Box 155)
        - Conflict of Interest (Box 155)
      - Lehman Brothers, 2001-2004 (Box 155)
      - Leveraging Procurement Team (LPT), 2002-2003 (Box 155)
      - Library, 2002 (Box 155)
      - Life Insurance Rates, 2003 (Box 155)
      - Life Sciences Institute, 2002 (Box 155)
      - LinkMichigan, 2002 (Box 155)
      - Listening Post, 2000-2001 (Box 155)
      - Literature, Science and Arts, College of, 2002-2004 (Box 155)
      - Loans to UM Employees, 2001-2002 (Box 155)
      - Loans to University Units, 1999-2000 (Box 155)
      - Local Municipalities, 2002 (Box 155)
      - Long Term Disability Rates (LTD), 1999-2000 (Box 155)
      - MCard
        - 2002 (Box 155)
        - 2003 (Box 155)
      - MCare, 1994-2004
        - Payroll Deduction Copay (Box 155)
        - 2004 (Box 155)
        - 2003, 2 folders (Box 156)
        - MCaid, 2 folders (Box 156)
        - Lockbox and Bank Accounts (Box 156)
        - PPO / HRA Products (Box 156)
        - Semi-Annual Tax Committee Meeting (Box 156)
      - M-Quality, 2000 (Box 156)
      - MPathways, 2001-2002
        - 2003 (Box 156)
        - 2002 (Box 156)
        - Financial / Physical Resources (Box 156)
        - Go-Delay Decision (Box 156)
        - Core Process Management Team (CPMT) (Box 156)
        - Updates (Box 156)
        - Help Desk (Box 156)
      - MPathways HRMS, 2001-2002
        - 2002 (Box 156)
        - Benefit Deduction Timing (Box 156)
        - DS Pay (Box 156)
        - Internal Controls (Box 156)
        - Status Report (Box 156)
        - Strategy (Box 156)
        - U-Year Salary Issue (Box 156)
        - United Way (Box 156)
      - Major Maintenance Plan, 2001-2003 (Box 156)
      - Martin Luther King Day, 2001-2002 (Box 156)
      - Medical School, 1999-2003
        - General (Box 156)
        - Building Plan (Box 156)
        - Financial Report (Box 156)
        - Journals (Box 156)
        - Spend Analysis (Box 156)
      - Medical Service Plan Audit, 2002 (Box 156)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (MHRI), 2002 (Box 156)
      - Merchant Acquirer Card, 2001-2002 (Box 156)
      - Michigan Administrative Information Services (MAIS), 1998-2004
        - General (Box 156)
        - Business and Finance Information Technology (BFIT) (Box 156)
        - BFIT Computer Equipment (Box 157)
        - BFIT Network Systems (Box 157)
        - Detailed Organization Design, 2 folders (Box 157)
        - Shared Services Organization, 2 folders (Box 157)
        - Strategic Plan and Capital Request (Box 157)
      - Michigan Health Corporation (MHC), 2002-2004; 2 folders (Box 157)
      - Michigan Life Science Purchasing Consortium (MLSPC), 2002 (Box 157)
      - Michigan Minority Business Development Council (MMBDC), 2002 (Box 157)
      - Michigan Provider Network (MPN), 2002 (Box 157)
      - Michigan Student Assembly (MSA), 2002 (Box 157)
      - Michigan Union Board of Representatives, 1999-2002 (Box 157)
      - Morgan Linen, 2003-2004 (Box 157)
      - Moving Expenses, 1999-2000 (Box 157)
      - Museum of Art, University, 2004 (Box 157)
      - Music, School of, 2002 (Box 157)
      - NACUBO (National Association of College and University Business Officers)
        - 2003 (Box 157)
        - 2002 (Box 157)
        - Cost Study (Box 157)
      - Natural Resources and Environment, School of, 2001-2003 (Box 157)
      - Naval Research, Office of -- Audit, 2002 (Box 157)
      - North Campus, 2003 (Box 157)
      - Omega Bayview IV, 2002 (Box 157)
      - Online Learning-Fanthom, 2001 (Box 157)
      - Online Policies Project, 2002 (Box 157)
      - Palmer Drive Development, 2002 (Box 157)
      - Pfizer, 2001 (Box 157)
      - Pharmacy, School of, 2003 (Box 157)
      - Power Michigan, 2002 (Box 157)
      - Privacy Oversight, 2004 (Box 157)
      - Professional Development Programs, 2001-2003 (Box 157)
      - Public Health, School of, 2000-2003 (Box 158)
        - General (Box 158)
        - Quasi-Endowment / Building (Box 158)
        - Investigation (Box 158)
      - Regents, 2002-2005
        - 2004 (Box 158)
        - 2003 (Box 158)
        - 2002, 2 folders (Box 158)
        - Presentation, July 2003 (Box 158)
        - Presentation, July 2001 (Box 158)
        - Finance, Audit and Investment Committee
          - General, 3 folders (Box 158)
          - Hospitals and Health Centers (HHC) Capital Plan Presentation (Box 158)
        - Hospitals and Health Centers (Box 158)
        - Sub-Committees (Box 158)
      - Research, 2000-2004
        - General (Box 158)
        - Human Subject Compliance (Box 158)
        - Signature Authority (Box 158)
        - Solar Car (Box 158)
      - Retirees Association, UM, 2001-2002 (Box 159)
      - Service Level Agreements, 2001-2003
        - General (Box 159)
        - Accounts Payable (Box 159)
        - Credit Card (Box 159)
        - Merchant Credit Card Payments (Box 159)
        - Other (Box 159)
        - Property Control (Box 159)
        - Supply Chain (Box 159)
        - Tagging / Inventory (Box 159)
      - Spirituality Center, 2002 (Box 159)
      - State Appropriation, 2001-2004
        - General, 2 folders (Box 159)
        - Senator Schwartz (Box 159)
      - State Building Authority Project, 2001-2002
        - General (Box 159)
        - Dana Building (Box 159)
        - Dearborn College of Arts, Sciences & Letters (Box 159)
        - Dearborn Environmental Center (Box 159)
        - Mason and Haven Halls (Box 159)
        - Perry Building (Box 159)
        - West Hall (Box 159)
      - Student and Exchange Visitor Information Systems Program (SEVIS), 2002 (Box 159)
      - Student Publications, 2001-2003; 2 folders (Box 159)